[
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "How much do you ... me on a scale of 1-10?",
    "answer": "trust"
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Harry lived in the cupboard under the stairs at number ... Privet Drive.",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "I have an insatiable ... to be right next to you ☺️",
    "answer": "desire"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The girl was barely ... years old when destiny bound her to Geralt.",
    "answer": 15
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "When you know about something it stops being a nightmare. When you know how to ... something, it stops being so threatening.",
    "answer": "fight"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "You did all the level ... in solo )",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "I think it's pretty irrational getting aroused about ... times now since we started talking. Despite kind of ghosting me. )",
    "answer": 6
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "In the year ..., the galaxy teeters on the brink of chaos",
    "answer": 3143
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "After all this time?” — ....",
    "answer": "always"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Well sometimes it feels like torture that I can’t ... you",
    "answer": "touch"
  }
]
